Now what we could do at the top of our contract, we can just say Boolean, private, s underscore is open.
现在我们可以在合约的顶部这样做，`bool private s_isOpen`
And we can just set this to true if we're open otherwise false.
我们把它设置为开放时为 true 反之为 false
Well, what if we have a ton of different states?
但如果我们有很多种不同的状态呢？
What if we want it to be like pending, open, closed, calculating, etc? What do we have a ton of different states?
如果我们想要有：“等待”("pending")，“开放”("open")，“关闭”("closed")，“计算中”("calculating")，等等这么多不同的状态呢？
Well, we could make this a U and 256. Private s underscore state.
我们可以把这个设置为 `uint256 private s_state`
And we could just keep track of the state having like zero b pending a one reopen to be closed, three, be calculating, etc.
我们可以通过把 "pending" 设置为 0, "open" 为 1, "closed" 为 2, "calculating" 为 3 来跟踪状态
But this can be a little tricky to keep track of.
但这样追踪可能会有些麻烦
So a better way to actually keep track of all this in our code is to use an enum
因此，在代码中更好的跟踪方式是使用“枚举”("Enum")
enums, can be used to create custom types with a finite set of constant values.
Enum 可以用于创建具有一组有限常量的自定义类型
So we can create, for example, a state created locked inactive, and it's basically a new type for a smart contract
我们可以这样创建，例如 "State "，它是智能合约中的一种新类型
for us, we're going to create a new type.
对我们来说，要做的就是创建一种新的类型
And if we go back to the layout of variables, and our smart contract
我们回到智能合约的变量布局这里
types should actually be first thing in our contract.
类型("Type") 应该作为我们合约中的第一部分
So we're going to create an E new called raffle state.
我们创建一个 `enum RaffleState`
And for now, and we're just going to have it be open,
目前我们只有 `Open`
we're just gonna have to be open or calculating.
我们只有 `OPEN` 和 `CALCULATING`
Now when we create an enum like this,
当我们像这样创建了一个 enum 时
we're kind of secretly creating a un 256, where zero equals open, and one equals calculating.
我们实际上就是创建了一个 `uint256 0 = OPEN, 1 = CALCULATING`
However, this is much more explicit that we know what each one of these numbers actually means.
然而，这样做更加明确，我们能知道每个数字实际上代表的意义
Now that we've created this new type called raffle state,
我们已经创建了一种名为 "RaffleState" 的新类型
we can create a new lottery state variable of type raffle state.
现在我们就可以创建一个新的状态变量，其类型就为 "RaffleState"
So the exact same way we declare any other variable,
就和我们声明其它变量一样
we'll name its type, which is going to be raffle state.
先写出它的类型，也就是 `RaffleState`
And this is going to be a storage variable. So we'll go ahead and do private s underscore raffle state
并且这是一个 storage 变量，所以就是 `private s_raffleState`
in our constructor, right when we launched this contract, we should open up this raffle.
在构造函数中，当我们启动这个合约时，我们应该开放抽奖
So we'll say s, raffle state equals and we could use a un 256. Wrapped in type raffle state like so.
所以我们写 `s_raffleState =` 我们可以用一个 uint256 包装进 `RaffleState` 就像这样
Or we can be more explicit and say raffle state DOT open.
或者我们可以更明确一些 `RaffleState.OPEN`
Now we know that the raffle state is in an open state
现在我们就知道 "RaffleState" 处于 "OPEN" 状态了
and we only want checkup keep to work is if the lottery is actually open.
我们希望只有当抽奖开放时 "checkUpkeep" 才会运行
Additionally, we probably only want people to be able to enter if the law battery's open.
并且，我们还希望只有在抽奖处于开放状态时才允许人们参与
So let's go ahead and create another if statement and revert if the lottery isn't open.
因此，让我们创建一组 "if" 语句，并在抽奖未开放时执行回滚操作
So we can say if s underscore raffle state does not equal raffle state DOT open,
所以我们说 `if (s_raffleState != RaffleState.OPEN)
then we're going to revert with a new error, we're going to create raffle underscore underscore, not open.
然后 `revert` 回滚一种将要创建的新错误类型 `Raffle__NotOpen`
And of course, at the top will create error, raffle not open.
当然了，要在顶部创建一个 `error Raffle__NotOpen`
Now additionally, let's go down when we're requesting a random word.
接着让我们来到下面，当我们请求一个随机数的时候
Let's update the state to be calculating so other people can't jump in here.
我们要更新状态为 "CALCULATING" 这样其它人就无法参与了
So right above our VRF coordinator dot request, random words
所以，在 "vrfCoordinator.requestRandomWords" 上面
will do s underscore raffle state equals raffle state DOT calculating
我们执行 `s_raffleState = RaffleState.CALCULATING`
so that nobody can enter our lottery and nobody can trigger a new update.
这样就没有人能参与进我们的抽奖，也没人能触发新的更新了
And then once we fulfill after we pick our winner, we'll say s raffle state equals raffle state DOT open again.
然后一旦我们选出了优胜者，就可以再次说 `s_raffleState = RaffleState.OPEN`